<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>nickherrig</title>
    <link>https://nickherrig.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on nickherrig</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://nickherrig.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fundamentals: Give a Damn about Binary</title>
      <link>https://nickherrig.com/posts/binary/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nickherrig.com/posts/binary/</guid>
      <description>Welcome Back Ladies and Gents! Welcome back to The Fundamentals blog series. Where we have a conversation about technology concepts in a non-intimidating fashion. The ultimate goal? To lower the barrier to entry to the technology industry, and inspire technology craftspeople of the future.
If you haven&amp;rsquo;t read the the fundamentals introduction post, feel free to give it a skim
Before Reading Today we will be using Python as our programming language of choice to work through examples and help us learn!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fundamentals: Introduction</title>
      <link>https://nickherrig.com/posts/the-fundamentals-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nickherrig.com/posts/the-fundamentals-intro/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago a friends partner reached out wanting some advice on learning to program and getting a job in the technology industry.
 &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m currently a high school teacher (band director) and am looking to make the change to web development in the next year.&amp;rdquo;
 He was really excited about starting his career shift from a band director at the local high school to a hacker and software engineer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quotes</title>
      <link>https://nickherrig.com/quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nickherrig.com/quotes/</guid>
      <description>Stephen McCranie
 &amp;ldquo;The master has failed more times than the beginner has even tried.&amp;rdquo;
 William of Occam
 &amp;ldquo;It is vain to do with more what can be done with fewer.&amp;rdquo;
 Linus Torvalds
 &amp;ldquo;Talk is cheap. Show me the code&amp;rdquo;
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>